How long have you been in your job for?
你已经在现在的岗位上工作多久了？
If you’re climbing a career ladder, how long do you intend to stay on it?
如果你正在攀登职业阶梯，打算在这条路上走多久？
It’s hard to know when to jump ship and to do something different, and it’s even more problematic deciding whether to quit if you don’t have a new job to go to.
很难判断何时该跳槽去尝试新的领域，而如果还没找到下家就决定辞职，那更是难上加难。
In the past, a job for life was just that – something you did throughout your working life.
过去，“终身职业”名副其实——就是你整个职业生涯都在从事的工作。
Being loyal to one company came with many perks and job security.
对一家公司保持忠诚会带来诸多福利和工作稳定性。
But these days, there are many more opportunities to switch your career path, so it’s normal to have many jobs listed on your CV.
但如今，更换职业道路的机会变得更多，所以简历上罗列多份工作经历是很正常的事。
It’s accepted that our goals change, so quitting one job for another shows how versatile and adaptable we are.
人们的目标会不断变化，这一点已被普遍接受，因此为了另一份工作而辞职，恰恰能体现一个人的多才多艺和适应能力。
According to insurance firm LV, a worker in the UK will change employer every five years on average.
据英国LV保险公司的数据显示，英国职场人士平均每五年就会更换一次雇主。
In the US, it’s even shorter, with people staying with a single employer for just over four years, according to official statistics.
官方统计数据表明，在美国，这个周期更短，人们在同一位雇主手下的工作时长仅略超四年。
Victoria Bethlehem from recruitment firm Adecco told the BBC that she looks favourably on a prospective employee who has changed roles every three to five years.
德科招聘公司的维多利亚·伯利恒在接受BBC采访时表示，她对那些每三到五年就更换一次岗位的潜在雇员抱有好感。
While it’s good to pursue new work challenges, is quitting your job for no job at all career suicide?
虽然追求新的工作挑战是件好事，但没找到下家就辞职，算得上是职业自杀吗？
It’s risky, but it can give you a chance to follow your dreams.
这种做法确实有风险，但它能给你一个追逐梦想的机会。
LinkedIn influencer Murugan Pandian, who’s a project efficiency expert at St Joseph’s Hospital Health Center, says: “If you are that miserable [in your job], then sometimes it helps to quit, reassess your priorities in life and then come up with a more creative job-hunting strategy.”
领英网红、圣约瑟夫医院健康中心的项目效率专家穆鲁甘·潘迪安表示：“如果你在当前工作中已经痛苦到这种地步，那么有时候辞职是有用的——你可以重新评估自己的人生优先级，然后制定出更有创意的求职策略。”
Of course resigning from your job is scary – there is the fear of the unknown, but for some, no job is better than a thankless one.
当然，辞职这件事本身是令人恐慌的——人们总会对未知的事物感到恐惧，但对有些人来说，失业也比做一份费力不讨好的工作要强。
The recent Covid pandemic has certainly made people think twice about their career priorities, and with workers being forced back to the office, some of them may be tempted to leave their job without having a new role to go to.
近年来的新冠疫情无疑让人们重新审视自己的职业优先级，而随着企业强制员工重返办公室，有些人可能会忍不住在没找到新工作的情况下就离职。
But no job means no money, so quitting needs careful thought, although it could lead you down a whole new career path.
但失业意味着没有收入，所以辞职需要深思熟虑，不过，这也可能引领你踏上一条全新的职业道路。